you
hey gang welcome to another free energy
video now many of my subscribers as well
as other viewers have been asking me to
look into a very popular and newer free
energy device shown on YouTube and
that's exactly what you're looking at
right over here according to the person
that produce these videos if you take a
neodymium magnet a plastic insulator as
well as a metal spring and a steel tube
you should be able to produce three
volts DC between the tip and the magnet
using that three volt DC you should be
able to drive a three volt LED as well
as this light here this is a 3 volt
light we're going to be trying that out
and then he also claims that you'll be
able to charge up your cell phone if you
connect a couple of these in parallel to
boost the current or in series to raise
the voltage so we're going to be taking
a look to see if this actually works as
shown in the other videos on YouTube or
if it's nothing more than pure let's
take a look they call this device a
magnetic resonator supposedly the
magnetic field is being captured within
this metal coil and it's producing DC
voltage it's also claimed that what you
see right here is referred to as a
electrosmog generator all very
interesting names but does it actually
work for this testing I'm going to be
using the mus tool MTA to six digital
multimeter you see right here it's set
for DC volts right now after I check the
voltage of this device I'm going to
discuss a few things which I observed in
the other videos ok let's take a look at
the voltage here alright so from the
bottom let's go to the top of this
insulator
nothing about the spring nothing in
handout from the top and look at that we
have three point zero nine volts but
there's nothing on the spring here and I
can go from the top of the magnet
because the magnet is all one nickel
plated finish that wraps all the way
around so you don't even have to test
the voltage from the backside because
it's all one piece as continuity 309
nothing there alright so let's go to the
continuity setting now and let's go
continuity alarm so this is going to be
one piece clearly alright and so is this
piece here now let's go between here and
the top hmm ok so there's nothing
between here and there because as the
other person has indicated you have this
insulator between the metal spring and
the neodymium magnet let me put this
down for a minute let's see if I get the
voltage off of this free energy
generator to light up the 10 millimeter
3 volt ultra bright white LED
Wow look at that right that is all right
so that works interesting and right over
here we'll be using a 3 volt
incandescent and you can see right here
lighting up nice fall off of the
wonderful free energy generator so now
you're going to say how could this
possibly work and how can this right
here not be conductive if there's
voltage at the top and it's making the
connection between top and bottom let me
make this extremely extremely clear just
like many other videos on YouTube I know
a lot of you do not like to hear it it
is nothing more than a scam to get views
so they can make money through
advertising
it is 100% impossible for a neodymium
magnet with an insulator with a spring
on the opposite side and a metal tube on
top to be able to produce any voltage in
order to produce voltage using a
magnetic field it cannot be stationary
it needs to be a rotating magnetic field
and you're going to have an alternating
current output you are not going to have
a direct current output the only way
this could possibly be done besides
using a video editor which I could have
done is in between here this little
piece this is not an insulator in order
for this to work there has to be a cell
or a battery located between the
neodymium magnet and that spring the
next thing you're going to ask is how
come there's no electricity here well
it's very simple you take some clear
coat you spray it over the spring
surface so when you go to check the
voltage it does not show up because you
have that thin layer of enamel
preventing the connection between the
top of the battery and the spring so
this clear coat here but on top there is
not it's also very funny that the person
shows 3 volts
which just so happens to be the voltage
of a very very thin and very small watch
battery I use a 3 volt watch battery and
I'll show you in a minute it's inside
here but there are technologies that are
out and it's possible this person may
have access to this newer technology
from someone that he knows they have
produced batteries which are extremely
extremely thin film looks like right
over here this one was produced by Rice
University and you can see it is just a
black film so I'm using a very thin
right here lithium battery 3 volt it's
very very tiny and I've seen what he
pulls it off sometimes it's thicker and
sometimes it is very thin so more than
likely what he did one of those free
energy generators uses a 3 volt button
cell and the other one uses a 1.5 volt
button cell and when you put the two
together you end up with around four and
a half volts if you have any doubt I
suggest you speak to a physics professor
and they will explain it to you very
clearly and they'll look at my video and
say he is 100% correct now take a look
over here alright what so there's the
battery let me put this back to
continuity again it was on it alright so
in the other video he tested it between
here and there after it was removed and
he went oh look at this it don't work
but then he does this he goes he goes oh
when it's disconnected it works but when
it's connected to the insulator it no
longer conduct yeah which is pure pure
all right so this right here same thing
metal tube spring this is very very thin
he also goes like this when he removes
it this was on the battery like that
this has a very thin little wire here
you could paint it black
and it will still make a connection so I
can go like this all right to hide it
and when the spring touches it it'll
scrape that little bit of black off of
the wire allowing it to make a
connection so he checks between here and
there all right it gets nothing
using a continuity setting and when he
does the voltage check let's go back
here
keep in mind you only have to touch a
very small area of the magnet you could
touch it anywhere it won't show up as a
voltage unless you touch it in the right
spot so it's very very easy to hide that
and you will not be charging any cell
phone using this device I hope you
enjoyed this video if you did please
rate it a thumbs up subscribe and post
links to this video on other websites
and blogs also be sure to check out my
video playlists as well thank you very
much for watching